

Hugo Dorfling

Full Stack Software Engineer

Location:Johannesburg, South AfricaDate of Birth:1995 / 03 / 15Languages:English & AfrikaansEmail:hugodorfling@live.co.zaPortfolio:www.hugo.dorfling.org

Education

Certifications

- AWS Developer Associate
- AWS Solutions Architect Associate
- · AWS Cloud Practitioner
- CompTIA A+
- CompTIA N+
- freeCodeCamp JavaScript Algorithms & Data Structures
- freeCodeCamp Responsive Web Design

University of Pretoria

BCom Informatics (1st year - Incomplete)

- Attended from Jan. 2017 to Nov. 2017
- Left to work full-time in IT to pivot to Computer Science studies
- 83.20% average semester 1

Hoërskool Eldoraigne

National Senior Certificate

- High school education from Jan. 2009 to Dec. 2013
- 87% average final mark

Personal Profile

Delivering value in roles ranging from product management, business analysis, design but mainly specialising in front-end and back-end development to build products customers love.

Dedicated to creatively analyse, design and invent technology solutions that solve real problems. I care passionately about providing tangible results, without sacrificing artistry and elegant design.

My persistent drive towards growth and knowledge motivates me to learn new technologies, adapt and grow, with a tremendous pace!

I really value progress.
I am focused on leaving a legacy and living well examined life.

Career Summary

Software Engineer

Synthesis Software Technologies Sep. 2020 to present

- Design and develop FinTech software products
- SaaS and Cloud Native
- Product design (UX/UI)
- Product management

Product Manager

Howler Jul. 2019 to Feb. 2020

- Tasked to ensure success of the company buying and taking over the IP of their cashless system software
- Product management
- Business Analysis
- Agile product delivery

LinkedIn: @leslie-hugo-dorfling

Professional Skills

Coding Languages:

C#, JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, SQL, C

Frameworks/Systems:

.Net Core, Entity Framework Core, React (Redux), Bootstrap, MySQL

Technologies:

Docker, Kubernetes, AWS, Unix, Git, Bitbucket, Unity, Blender

Tools/Processes:

Miro, Figma (Design & Prototyping), Jira, Confluence, Microsoft Teams, Test driven development

Soft skills:

Assertive, Excellent Communicator (Written & Verbal), Strong interpersonal skills (flexible & tolerant), Negotiation, Influencing, Fast learner, Exceptional analytical problem solving ability, Planning, Leadership, Project Management

Character References

Terence Palani